[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fashion house Hermes named their famous Birkin bag after Jane Birkin. Who is she?", "correct_answer": "an English actress and singer", "incorrect_answers": ["a French painter and sculptor", "an Italian model", "an American tennis player"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Body Mass Index (BMI) is the relation between body mass and height.  If your BMI is in this range then you are considered overweight.", "correct_answer": "25 to 29.9", "incorrect_answers": ["20 to 24.9", "15 - 19.9", "10 - 14.9"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following statements about quadrilaterals (4-sided figures) is true?", "correct_answer": "A square is a type of parallelogram.", "incorrect_answers": ["A parallelogram is a type of trapezoid.", "A rhombus is a type of rectangle.", "A rectangle is a type of square."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Boeing 747 project was so big, that there were no buildings that could house it.  Boeing constructed the largest building in the world for this purpose.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Doc Brown, the inventor in the movie Back to the Future, makes a time machine out of a Lamborghini.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Parts of the plant Helianthus annuus are edible.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "We get this very popular word from one of Athenas aliases in Greek mythology.", "correct_answer": "mentor", "incorrect_answers": ["computer", "media", "lesbian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Elephants always give birth to twins.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Located along the Martian equator, Valles Marineris is a canyon much bigger than the Grand Canyon on Earth. How long is it?", "correct_answer": "4,000 km long.", "incorrect_answers": ["750 km long.", "Just under 500 km long.", "2,500 km long."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the character played by Dustin Hoffman in The Graduate?", "correct_answer": "Benjamin Braddock", "incorrect_answers": ["Benjamin Williams", "Benjamin Billings", "Benjamin Smith"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Shakespearean play is referred to as The Scottish Play or The Scottish King by most actors and theater people since it is considered bad luck to mention the name of the play.", "correct_answer": "Macbeth", "incorrect_answers": ["King Lear", "Othello", "Hamlet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of herbs are used in traditional Chinese medicine to trigger sweating and invigorate blood?", "correct_answer": "Pungent herbs", "incorrect_answers": ["Sour herbs", "Bitter herbs", "Sweet herbs"]}]